I didn't even get out of my pads yet.
>> Leonard coach said he wanted you guys to
be focused and loose.
>> Yeah,
>> you were a lot more than that.
>> that just doesn't cover it, doesn't it?
I mean, other words, what would you use?
>> I would say relentless, locked in. Um,
but the loose and focus thing that, you
know, Mike talks about, uh, I think this
team really embodies that. Um, you know,
I've been telling everybody as soon as
I, you know, started working with Mike
and Schneider and, uh, being a part of
this team, uh, it reminds me of my young
days when I was in college, when I was
in high school, and it's just like guys
are just playing for the love of the
game. Um, not, you know, in the NFL
sometimes you see people on different
agendas. Sometimes it's about money,
sometimes their family, you know, all
these different things. There's a bunch
of grown men, um, you know, that have
their own agendas. But, uh, on this
team, our agenda is each other, um, and
and this team. And uh I think we really
embody that.
>> You think you guys rank up there with
the great defenses in history?
>> I mean I think so. I mean I think we did
a tremendous job today. Um we were
honestly mad that they scored it all. We
were trying to get a shut out in the
Super Bowl. Make make history and uh put
a stamp on that dark side defense that
we've had this year. Um we did a great
job getting after the quarterback.
Unfortunately my sack was taken away at
the end. Um but I'm just so proud of the
guys, man. Uh it's not about me. Um, I'm
just happy that, you know, we did such a
great job today.
>> I honestly got in there late because I
was doing some stuff with the NFL uh,
media and stuff like that, but by the
time I got in there, it was I couldn't
see, I couldn't breathe. It was kind of
smoked out from cigars and um, I think
every position group has their own like
set of ski goggles. I got the whole D
line, some Chrome Hearts ones, you know,
I had to up everybody. Um, but it's just
amazing see her and everybody smile. Um,
I think that's what makes this moment so
special for me is just uh seeing my
teammates that have put the work in, put
the grind in, and uh, everybody on this
team deserves it.
>> Speaking of the work that you guys put
in, you saw Sam and Sam, the Jets. How
proud are you to see him?
>> I mean, super proud of him. He's had
doubters his whole life. He's had a lot
of ups and downs. Had a tremendous
journey. And, uh, I think one thing
about him, he he's been unwavering
through it all. Um he's never let one
doubter uh skew his mindset, change who
he is, and uh he's just a tremendous
leader and uh you know, he brought us to
the Super Bowl and won the Super Bowl.
And um you know, I can't say I can't say
anything more about that guy. He's just
a great guy.
>> Establish a pass rush back.
>> I mean, I think our secondary did a
tremendous job of uh covering in the
back end. Um, I think it forced Drake to
hold on to the ball. Um, and it allowed
us time to get after the quarterback.
Um, you know, throughout the playoffs,
we seen that that was something that,
uh, we were able to exploit. Um, you
know, they they played against great
defenses throughout the whole playoffs,
uh, in Denver and Houston. And, uh, you
know, both of those defenses were able
to sack him a few times. And, uh, you
know, being a quarterback, you're you're
the head of the offense, you're the head
of the team. So, uh, if you take the
head out, um, you know, the rest will
follow. and um we just felt like he was
the guy that we had to attack.
>> I mean, it was all about just collapsing
the inside of the pocket. Um we have
some, you know, great detackles. Um you
know, Byron Murphy got two sacks today.
Uh we had like just great middle middle
presence, middle middle push. Uh he
obviously was able to escape a few
times, but you know, that's going to
happen in the game. Uh overall I think
we were on his toes all game.
>> You guys did a number on the left side
of their offensive line. Was that
something that was like during the prep?
>> Yeah, you know they had a veteran um
right tackle. Um I think 71. I have a
lot of respect for him. He's a great
guard. Uh big heavy guy. Um and I you
know they have a young offensive line on
the left side and uh we knew that that
was an area we wanted to attack.
>> Was there anything you guys didn't
just like
I mean, I think we just did what we do
all year. Um, that's something we've
been saying for the last two weeks, uh,
preparing for this game is, um, you
know, all we have to do is be us, but we
have to be us. That's that's been our
slogan um, you know, pretty much all
season is, um, it's it's not about the
other team, it's about us. And when we
perform at our highest level, when we
have guys um, doing their role to their
best of their ability,
>> we feel like we can't be touched.
out today, but how much of a team is he?
>> You say Ernest Jones.
>> Yeah, I mean, he's been a great addition
to this team. Uh we got him mid-season
last year and he he made an immediate
impact. Um and you know, to be able to
come in at middle linebacker and take
lead of a defense that you didn't know.
Uh that speaks volumes on his character
and uh his leadership. Um, you know, he
has he gained a lot of respect from from
the locker room and uh I was honestly
surprised to find out that he was only
like 25 this year or something like that
cuz I thought he was about my age the
way he carries himself.
>> How does it feel right now reflecting on
where you are right now?
>> I mean honestly it's uh I'm still
soaking it in. Um it's just it's been
like a kind of a roller coaster since
the game ended of um you know realizing
that we won the Super Bowl and and it
not hitting me at the same time. It's
like I know it's going to hit me uh for
the next few weeks. Um but it just the
journey means a lot. It's it's what
makes this moment feel so special. Um
not just my own individual journey of uh
you know being injured, being traded, uh
all types of things, you know, being on
a lot of losing seasons and all that
stuff. Um but also just our journey that
we've had as a team this year. Um and
it's it's been beautiful. It's been a
dream this year.
>> What's that?
>> I mean, yeah, once once we got to
halftime and there was uh zero points.
Um I think we came out of halftime
saying we have enough points to win the
game. Um we don't need any more points.
As a defense, we take pride in uh
stopping offenses and uh you know, we've
been calling ourselves the dark side
this year and I we thought that that was
going to put a stamp. Um I think we
still did put a stamp on on who we are
uh and put a stamp on the dark side, but
uh we were definitely seeking that uh
that goose egg.
>> Uh we just came up with that name
because uh you know, we've had a
tremendous defense this year. Um, and
people were, you know, comparing us to
the Legion of the Boom. And we have a
lot of respect for the Legion of Boom.
We have a lot of respect for all the
players on that on that defense. They
were a tremendous team, a tremendous
defense. And, uh, we we wanted our own
name. We wanted to respect um, you know,
the guys who have been here before, the
guys who have laid the foundation, and
also respect the guys on our team right
now who are, you know, creating a new
standard. And, uh, by respecting our our
new standard, uh, we wanted to put a
label on it.
>> Here comes here comes the Northern
California question. your journey
involved with your time in Sacramento.
>> Uh not too much. Uh I was, you know, I
bounced around a lot as a kid growing
up. Uh another part of my journey, which
is uh been kind of crazy. Uh my wife
knows my story a bit, but um I was in
and out of homeless shelters with my
family, in hotels, motel. Uh we bounced
all over the country. Um
>> and uh yeah, it's just been that's
another part of my journey that makes
this moment so special.
a lot of
>> Sorry. Thank you guys.